

#### **PROFILE**

A computer technical professional with 29 years of experience in web design and development and data analysis, he has served in various naval units, where he formed and continues to form part of work teams in which leadership and teamwork are essential elements of the individual.

### **CONTACT**

PHONO: 991 906 830

ADDRESS:

Asoc. De Propietarios Las Brisas de Naranjal Mz. A Lote 29 - SMP

**EMAIL** 

absalon.malafay@gmail.com

#### **LANGUAGE**

**Spanish:** Native **English:** basic

"The most important responsibility of anyone attempting to manage anything is to manage themselves first."

# ABSALON MALAFAY VELA

DNI 43251440

# **WEB ANALYST PROGRAMMER**

#### **TECHNICAL TRAINING**

# INSTITUTO SUPERIOR TECNOLÓGICO PÚBLICO NAVAL

PROCESAMIENTO DE DATOS - CITEN (1998-2000)

#### **TRAINING**

#### **PERUVIAN NAVY**

NAVAL TEACHING AND INSTRUCTOR COURSE (2004) ADVANCED DATA PROCESSING SCHOOLS (2015) GOVERNMENT CONTRACTS (2017) IA ELEMENTS (2024))

## SCHOOL OF TELECOMMUNICATIONS - INICTEL

NETWORK ENGINEERING - WINDOWS SERVER 2000 (2002) STRUCTURED CABLING SPECIALIST (2003)

#### **TELEMATIC**

WEBSITE DESIGN (2006)

#### **GRADUATE SCHOOL - USIL**

EXECUTIVE PROFESSIONALIZATION IN STRATEGIC LEADERSHIP (2015)

#### **CONSULTANCY - ITEC**

BASIC EXCEL ADVANCED EXCEL BASIC PYTHON

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- Responsible for the design, development, and administration of the Peruvian Navy website (2006-2008)
- Responsible for the design and development of the DIRCOMAT-MGP Guarantee System (2016-2018)
- Development of the DIALI-MGP Naval Maintenance System (2019-present)

#### **OTHER KNOWLEDGE**

- DATA ANALYSIS WITH POWER BI
- LMS-MOODLE-CHAMILO
- PHP LARAVEL REACT
- HTML-CSS- BOOTSTRAP-MVC
- WORDPRESS DIVI ECOMMERCE -PHP
- VISUAL STUDIO C# DEVEXPRESS-SQL

# **SKILLS**

- Critical Thinking
- Soft Skills
- Leadership
- Teamwork, Multitasking
- Innovation
- Time Management